Okorie Wisdom

frontend developer // HTML // Css // JavaScript // React js

Website: [PORTFOLIO:https://illustrious-nasturtium.netlify.app/]

Email: wisdomokorie18@gmail.com

How can I help you, I'm wisdom okorie by name, I'm a frontend developer with the following skills; HTML, CSS, JavaScript, bootstrap and React js. i have worked on alot of projects which also include changing and converting the templet of an already built website and building cool projects from stretch too. you can check out my portfolio at my bio

EXPERIENCE

Shinarium Jan 2022 - Present ·

worked on a project which include changing and converting the templet of an already built website

I worked on an already made html, CSS and JavaScript templet and made it look absolutely different.. the site is live and you can check on it at my portfolio.

Upwork Sep 2021 to Jan 2022

Freelance frontend web developer

Xenon Jul 2020 to Apr 2021

Junior frontend developer

EDUCATION

Ebonyi state university

2018 to 2022

Bachelor of computer science

SKILLS

Web Development, Front-End Development, Collaborated with other team member to achieve target results, Coded website using HTML CSS AND JAVASCRIPT, Create responsive website with react js, Collaborative Problem Solving, HTML, React Hooks, coded using wordpress and visual studio software to create responsive website, React.js, HTML5, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Bootstrap, JavaScript, English